B2.
Daniel has also found a talk about why wild animals are in danger.
Listen with him and complete the notes below.
Wild animals are in danger for many reasons.
One reason is natural.
For example, it is difficult for some special kinds of wild animals to have babies and they may get sick easily and die.
Natural disasters like floods can also be a problem for wild animals.
However, human activities are the biggest reason.
People take lots of land for their own use so many animals lose their living spaces.
Air pollution and water pollution also make it difficult for animals to live healthy lives.
Moreover, human activities are warming the earth and serious weather events happen more often.
As a result, certain wild animals may not have a place to live or enough food to eat.
Hunting is another big problem for wild animals.
People hunt them for food and their fur, bones or other parts of the body.
All of these make it hard for animals to survive in the wild.